koovs.com 2019-07-18

# Koovs Privacy Policy

The KOOVS (“we”, “our”, “us”) Privacy Policy aims at safe-guarding the confidentiality of our customers and site visitors (“you”, “your”, “yours”). We hereby declare that your details will not be disclosed to any third party unless it is required to provide a service to you. Please go through the below mentioned Privacy Policy points carefully. By accessing our website, you acknowledge reading and understanding the policies, and hence agree to be bound by the terms stated below.

### Your Consent

Your personal details (name, location, e-mail address, debit/credit card information) will not be sold or rented by us to any third party without your consent. Though we reserve the right to communicate your personal information to any third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure; we will not disclose your name, address and other information which identifies you personally to any third party without your consent. However, we hold no responsibility for any action of third party that may have directed you to our website.

### Communication & Marketing

If you become a registered member of KOOVS, you will be able to receive promotional emails regarding latest offers and discounts from us. You may also receive such communication if you have made a purchase as a guest user.

Please note that in case you don’t wish to receive such e-mails, you have the full liberty to opt-out of such communication any time. You can unsubscribe by visiting ‘My Details’ in ‘My Account’ if you are a registered user; or simply click on “to unsubscribe” link given in the mail.

### Cookies

We use cookies and other technologies such as pixel tags and clear gifs to store certain types of information each time you visit any page on our website. This enables us to determine what portions of this website are most appropriate for your professional needs and to serve advertising banners to you. You may choose to decline cookies, but this would disable the scope of experiencing the entire feature of the website. Hence, we recommend that you leave them turned on.

### Protecting Your Security

Please note that we may share your personal details with fraud prevention or credit reference agency for conducting anti-fraud checks. Please note that in this process no credit check is performed and your credit rating remains unaffected.

### Disclosures of your information

We may share your personal information with our other corporate entities to:

  * correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services;
  * facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity;
  * should such a transaction occur, that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information
  * We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.
  * As we use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet, they may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services to target advertisements for goods and services. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process.

### Usage of Demographic and Profile Data

We use your personal information to:

  * provide the services you request;
  * to resolve disputes & troubleshoot problems;
  * promote a safe service;
  * measure consumer interest in our products and services;
  * inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates;
  * request optional online surveys

Please note that we will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses.

### Third Party Sites

You may be linked to our website from our advertisers, network partners or any other third party. We hereby declare that we hold no liability or responsibility for the ‘Privacy Policies’ and ‘Terms & Conditions’ of these web sites. Please read their policies carefully before sharing any of your details.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on the Website. Hence, it is the responsibility of each user to review the website and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy.

For any queries or support, you may get in touch with our customer support team or mail us at [care@m-eretail.com](mailto:care@m-eretail.com)
